{"data":[{"question":"He required that Alice ___ the meeting.","a":"would attend","b":"attends","c":"attended","d":"attend","answer":"4","explain":"\n-The Subjunctive is used after the following verbs:to advise (that); to ask (that); to command (that); to demand (that); to desire (that); to insist (that); to propose (that), to recommend (that); to request (that); to suggest (that); to urge (that) \n- Structure: advise, ask, suggest (that)","category":"1","subcategorylv1":"50","subcategorylv2":"2","type":"1"},{"question":"If you _________ see Mr Allen, give him my regards.","a":"should","b":"would","c":"shall","d":"will","answer":"1","explain":"\n- Conditional Sentence Type 1: It is possible and also very likely that the condition will be fulfilled. \n- Form: if + Simple Present, will-Future \n- Should: used to say that you expect something to happen or be true","category":"1","subcategorylv1":"50","subcategorylv2":"2","type":"1"},{"question":"She is not supposed to play with us until the teacher recommends that she ___ allowed to do so.","a":"is","b":"be","c":"were","d":"will be","answer":"2","explain":"\n- The Subjunctive is used after the following verbs:to advise (that); to ask (that); to command (that); to demand (that); to desire (that); to insist (that); to propose (that), to recommend (that); to request (that); to suggest (that); to urge (that) \n- Structure: advise, ask, suggest (that)","category":"1","subcategorylv1":"50","subcategorylv2":"2","type":"1"},{"question":"You should have been to your sister's home! \" Yes, I ___.","a":"should","b":"ought to be","c":"must","d":"should have","answer":"4","explain":"- Should + have + pp:\u00a0used to say what was expected, but did not happen","category":"1","subcategorylv1":"50","subcategorylv2":"2","type":"1"},{"question":"If it ___ tomorrow, we will put off our picnic.","a":"rains","b":"will rain","c":"would rain","d":"rained","answer":"1","explain":"\n- Conditional Sentence Type 1: It is possible and also very likely that the condition will be fulfilled. \n+ Form: if + Simple Present, will-Future \n+ Should: used to say that you expect something to happen or be true","category":"1","subcategorylv1":"50","subcategorylv2":"2","type":"1"},{"question":"If you ___ help me, I should be very grateful to you.","a":"should","b":"would","c":"will","d":"can","answer":"2","explain":"\n- Conditional Sentence Type 2: It is possible but very unlikely, that the condition will be fulfilled. \n- Form: if + Simple Past, Conditional I (= would + Infinitive)","category":"1","subcategorylv1":"50","subcategorylv2":"2","type":"1"},{"question":"If a man doesn't remain content with what he has, ill ___ him.","a":"will befall","b":"befall","c":"hardly befall","d":"tell","answer":"1","explain":"\n- Conditional Sentence Type 1: It is possible and also very likely that the condition will be fulfilled. \n+Form: if + Simple Present, will-Future ","category":"1","subcategorylv1":"50","subcategorylv2":"2","type":"1"},{"question":"If you ___ me, I could find Jane is unaware of the fact.","a":"would have told","b":"told","c":"have told","d":"tell","answer":"2","explain":"\n- Conditional Sentence Type 2: It is possible but very unlikely, that the condition will be fulfilled. \n- Form: if + Simple Past, Conditional I (= would + Infinitive) ","category":"1","subcategorylv1":"50","subcategorylv2":"2","type":"1"},{"question":"Helen doesn't know how much I spent in repairing the house; if she ever found out, I am sure ___.","a":"she'd never forgive me","b":"she never forgives me","c":"she'll never forgive me","d":"she does not forgive me","answer":"1","explain":"\n- Conditional Sentence Type 2: It is possible but very unlikely, that the condition will be fulfilled. \n- Form: if + Simple Past, Conditional I (= would + Infinitive)","category":"1","subcategorylv1":"50","subcategorylv2":"2","type":"1"},{"question":"___ out of season, I would have ordered some from the fruit stand.","a":"If oranges would have been","b":"If oranges have not been","c":"Had oranges not been","d":"Should oranges not have been","answer":"3","explain":"\n- Conditional Sentence Type 3: It is impossible that the condition will be fulfilled because it refers to the past. \n- Form: if\/had + Past Perfect, Conditional II (= would + have + Past Participle) ","category":"1","subcategorylv1":"50","subcategorylv2":"2","type":"1"}]}